<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<LanguageData>
<!--=============== Amalgam Microfibral Muscle ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamMicrofibralMuscle.label>microfibral muscle</OE_AmalgamMicrofibralMuscle.label>
<OE_AmalgamMicrofibralMuscle.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene take less injuries than others from the same damage and feel half as much pain compared to a baseliner gene. They have extra-strong muscle fibers.</OE_AmalgamMicrofibralMuscle.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Armored Skeleton ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamArmoredSkeleton.label>armored skeleton</OE_AmalgamArmoredSkeleton.label>
<OE_AmalgamArmoredSkeleton.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene are not slowed down when taking damage and do more damage in close-quarters combat. They have thickened, densified bones, nearly-solid ribcages, and strengthened binding factors in joints and flesh.</OE_AmalgamArmoredSkeleton.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Temperature-Tolerant ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamTemperature.label>amalgam temperature-tolerant</OE_AmalgamTemperature.label>
<OE_AmalgamTemperature.labelShortAdj>amalgam-tolerant</OE_AmalgamTemperature.labelShortAdj>
<OE_AmalgamTemperature.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene are more comfortable in any temperatures. They have shielded temperature resistant skin layer.</OE_AmalgamTemperature.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Plating Skin ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamPlatingSkin.label>plating skin</OE_AmalgamPlatingSkin.label>
<OE_AmalgamPlatingSkin.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene have armored skin and are resistant to blast damage. They have shielded plating skin layer.</OE_AmalgamPlatingSkin.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Shielded Skin ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamShieldedSkin.label>shielded skin</OE_AmalgamShieldedSkin.label>
<OE_AmalgamShieldedSkin.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene are resistant to environmental toxins, toxic buildup, acid, cryo and flame damages from any sources. They have shielded flexible skin layer.</OE_AmalgamShieldedSkin.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Healing Factor ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamHealingFactor.label>healing factor</OE_AmalgamHealingFactor.label>
<OE_AmalgamHealingFactor.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene gain immunity to diseases considerably faster than normal and heal from wounds four times as fast as normal.</OE_AmalgamHealingFactor.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Psy-Sensitive ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamPsychicAbility.label>amalgam psy-sensitive</OE_AmalgamPsychicAbility.label>
<OE_AmalgamPsychicAbility.labelShortAdj>psy-amalgam</OE_AmalgamPsychicAbility.labelShortAdj>
<OE_AmalgamPsychicAbility.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene has the greatest psychically-sensitive. With great power comes great responsibility.</OE_AmalgamPsychicAbility.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Mech Domination ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamMechDomination.label>mech domination</OE_AmalgamMechDomination.label>
<OE_AmalgamMechDomination.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene have neuroenhancer allows to control many more mechanoids at once.</OE_AmalgamMechDomination.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Mech Exploiter ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamMechExploiter.label>mech exploiter</OE_AmalgamMechExploiter.label>
<OE_AmalgamMechExploiter.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene have neuroenhancer allows to control mechanoids more effective.</OE_AmalgamMechExploiter.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Hemogen Recovery ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamHemogenRecovery.label>hemogen recovery</OE_AmalgamHemogenRecovery.label>
<OE_AmalgamHemogenRecovery.resourceLabel>hemogen</OE_AmalgamHemogenRecovery.resourceLabel>
<OE_AmalgamHemogenRecovery.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene restores an additional 6 hemogen per day.</OE_AmalgamHemogenRecovery.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Eyes ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamEyes.label>amalgam eyes</OE_AmalgamEyes.label>
<OE_AmalgamEyes.description>Amalgam eyes improve the carrier's sight capacity and improves accuracy.</OE_AmalgamEyes.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Nervous System ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamNervousSystem.label>amalgam nervous system</OE_AmalgamNervousSystem.label>
<OE_AmalgamNervousSystem.description>Amalgam nervous system improve the carrier's consciousness capacity and improves negotiating abilities.</OE_AmalgamNervousSystem.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Fingers ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamFingers.label>amalgam fingers</OE_AmalgamFingers.label>
<OE_AmalgamFingers.description>Amalgam fingers improve the carrier's manipulation capacity. This aids with many tasks, especially crafting and construction.</OE_AmalgamFingers.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Tail ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamTail.label>amalgam tail</OE_AmalgamTail.label>
<OE_AmalgamTail.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene grow a tail that can act as a dexterous fifth limb.</OE_AmalgamTail.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Gene Flexibility ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamGeneFlexibility.label>amalgam gene flexibility</OE_AmalgamGeneFlexibility.label>
<OE_AmalgamGeneFlexibility.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene have special cellular structure that facilitate and optimize metabolism. This improves overall genetic and metabolic quality, but increases the market value significantly.</OE_AmalgamGeneFlexibility.description>

<!--=============== Amalgam Gene Filter ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamGeneDrugfilter.label>amalgam drugs filter</OE_AmalgamGeneDrugfilter.label>
<OE_AmalgamGeneDrugfilter.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene are immune to the torment of withdrawal, preventing the host from feeling any negative side effects from neglected addictions.\n\nIf you encounter a previously unknown substance, we recommend contacting your nearest Obsidia Empire support center on Steam to report the substance and its source.</OE_AmalgamGeneDrugfilter.description>

<!--=============== ISEKAI Memories ====================-->
<OE_AmalgamISEKAIMemories.label>ISEKAI Memories</OE_AmalgamISEKAIMemories.label>
<OE_AmalgamISEKAIMemories.description>Carriers of this amalgam gene display an unusual mix of behavior and recollection, as if their minds are stitched together from countless lifetimes.\n\nThey often drift into tales of distant worlds, claiming flashes of wisdom drawn from their “past reincarnations,” and can’t resist reminding others of the fateful day they were struck down by the legendary Truck-kun. To them, every campfire chat is a chance to retell their otherworldly beginnings.\n\nOnce per day the pawn gains both a positive and a negative buff, reflecting the chaotic echoes of their isekai memories.</OE_AmalgamISEKAIMemories.description>

</LanguageData>