<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
<!--=============== Ghoul Skin ====================-->
<OE_GhoulImplantSkin.label>ghoul skin implant - Carapace</OE_GhoulImplantSkin.label>
<OE_GhoulImplantSkin.description>Obsidia cultist skin implant for ghouls releases chemicals and nanomachines that toughen the skin and add flexible subdermal empyrium and orichalcum plates at strategic points. This makes the ghoul more resistant to damage across their whole body.\n\nDue to the extremely painful nature of the prosthetic, only ghouls can tolerate this implant.</OE_GhoulImplantSkin.description>

<!--=============== Ghoul Stomach ====================-->
<OE_GhoulImplantStomach.label>ghoul stomach implant - Larva</OE_GhoulImplantStomach.label>
<OE_GhoulImplantStomach.description>Obsidia cultist stomach implant for ghouls is installed under the stomach and integrated into the digestive system. Helps digest food more efficiently. This slightly reduces the ghoul's metabolism, causing it to eat less.\n\nDue to the extremely painful nature of the prosthetic, only ghouls can tolerate this implant.</OE_GhoulImplantStomach.description>

<!--=============== Ghoul Skeleton ====================-->
<OE_GhoulImplantSkeleton.label>ghoul skeleton implant - Scarab</OE_GhoulImplantSkeleton.label>
<OE_GhoulImplantSkeleton.description>Obsidia cultist skeleton implant for ghouls replaces all the bones in the body with stronger ones. This makes the ghoul unstoppable and more effective in melee combat.\n\nDue to the extremely painful nature of the prosthetic, only ghouls can tolerate this implant.</OE_GhoulImplantSkeleton.description>

<!--=============== Ghoul Head Prosthetic ====================-->
<CAC_GhoulProstheticHelmet.label>ghoul skull prosthetic - Crusader's Helmet</CAC_GhoulProstheticHelmet.label>
<CAC_GhoulProstheticHelmet.description>Obsidia cultist skull prosthetic for ghouls integrates brutally into the cranium and neural core, enhancing close-combat potential and significantly reinforcing the head against incoming damage.\n\nDue to the extremely painful nature of the prosthetic, only ghouls can tolerate this prosthetic.</CAC_GhoulProstheticHelmet.description>

<!--=============== Ghoul Shoulder Prosthetic ====================-->
<CAC_GhoulProstheticClaws.label>ghoul arm prosthetic - Crusader's Claws</CAC_GhoulProstheticClaws.label>
<CAC_GhoulProstheticClaws.description>Obsidia cultist arm prosthetic for ghouls replaces part of the arm with a massive mechanized combat claw, enabling the wearer to deliver devastating melee strikes and overwhelm most organic opponents.\n\nDue to the extremely painful nature of the prosthetic, only ghouls can tolerate this prosthetic.</CAC_GhoulProstheticClaws.description>

<!--=============== Ghoul Torso Prosthetic ====================-->
<CAC_GhoulProstheticChamber.label>ghoul body prosthetic - Crusader's Drive</CAC_GhoulProstheticChamber.label>
<CAC_GhoulProstheticChamber.description>Obsidia cultist body prosthetic for ghouls integrates a system of pumps and chemical reservoirs into the torso via spinal implantation, enabling the user to deploy two distinct chemical enhancers - one that accelerates movement and boosts melee damage, and another that reduces incoming damage and lowers susceptibility to fire.\n\nDue to the extremely painful nature of the prosthetic, only ghouls can tolerate this prosthetic.</CAC_GhoulProstheticChamber.description>

</LanguageData>