<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
<!--=============== Arms ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticArm.label>bionic arm</OE_ProstheticArm.label>
<OE_ProstheticArm.description>Obsidia bionic arm. It is better than a biological arm in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticArm.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticArm_M.label>advanced bionic arm</OE_ProstheticArm_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticArm_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic arm. It is much better than a biological arm in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticArm_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticArm_CAC.label>cultist bionic arm</OE_ProstheticArm_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticArm_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic arm. It is much better than a biological arm in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticArm_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticArm_OES.label>heroic bionic arm</OE_ProstheticArm_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticArm_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic arm. It is much better than a biological arm in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticArm_OES.description>

<!--=============== Legs ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLeg.label>bionic leg</OE_ProstheticLeg.label>
<OE_ProstheticLeg.description>Obsidia bionic leg. It is better than a biological leg in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLeg.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLeg_M.label>advanced bionic leg</OE_ProstheticLeg_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticLeg_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic leg. It is much better than a biological leg in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLeg_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLeg_CAC.label>cultist bionic leg</OE_ProstheticLeg_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticLeg_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic leg. It is much better than a biological leg in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLeg_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLeg_OES.label>heroic bionic leg</OE_ProstheticLeg_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticLeg_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic leg. It is much better than a biological leg in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLeg_OES.description>

<!--=============== Spine ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticSpine.label>bionic spine</OE_ProstheticSpine.label>
<OE_ProstheticSpine.description>Obsidia bionic spine. It is better than a biological spine in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticSpine.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticSpine_M.label>advanced bionic spine</OE_ProstheticSpine_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticSpine_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic spine. It is much better than a biological spine in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticSpine_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticSpine_CAC.label>cultist bionic spine</OE_ProstheticSpine_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticSpine_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic spine. It is much better than a biological spine in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticSpine_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticSpine_OES.label>heroic bionic spine</OE_ProstheticSpine_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticSpine_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic spine. It is much better than a biological spine in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticSpine_OES.description>

<!--=============== Stomach ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticStomach.label>bionic stomach</OE_ProstheticStomach.label>
<OE_ProstheticStomach.description>Obsidia bionic stomach. It is better than a biological stomach in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticStomach.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticStomach_M.label>advanced bionic stomach</OE_ProstheticStomach_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticStomach_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic stomach. It is much better than a biological stomach in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticStomach_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticStomach_CAC.label>cultist bionic stomach</OE_ProstheticStomach_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticStomach_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic stomach. It is much better than a biological stomach in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticStomach_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticStomach_OES.label>heroic bionic stomach</OE_ProstheticStomach_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticStomach_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic stomach. It is much better than a biological stomach in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticStomach_OES.description>

<!--=============== Heart ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticHeart.label>bionic heart</OE_ProstheticHeart.label>
<OE_ProstheticHeart.description>Obsidia bionic heart. It is better than a biological heart in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticHeart.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticHeart_M.label>advanced bionic heart</OE_ProstheticHeart_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticHeart_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic heart. It is much better than a biological heart in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticHeart_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticHeart_CAC.label>cultist bionic heart</OE_ProstheticHeart_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticHeart_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic heart. It is much better than a biological heart in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticHeart_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticHeart_OES.label>heroic bionic heart</OE_ProstheticHeart_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticHeart_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic heart. It is much better than a biological heart in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticHeart_OES.description>

<!--=============== Kidney ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticKidney.label>bionic kidney</OE_ProstheticKidney.label>
<OE_ProstheticKidney.description>Obsidia bionic kidney. It is better than a biological kidney in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticKidney.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticKidney_M.label>advanced bionic kidney</OE_ProstheticKidney_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticKidney_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic kidney. It is much better than a biological kidney in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticKidney_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticKidney_CAC.label>cultist bionic kidney</OE_ProstheticKidney_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticKidney_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic kidney. It is much better than a biological kidney in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticKidney_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticKidney_OES.label>heroic bionic kidney</OE_ProstheticKidney_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticKidney_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic kidney. It is much better than a biological kidney in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticKidney_OES.description>

<!--=============== Liver ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLiver.label>bionic liver</OE_ProstheticLiver.label>
<OE_ProstheticLiver.description>Obsidia bionic liver. It is better than a biological liver in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLiver.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLiver_M.label>advanced bionic liver</OE_ProstheticLiver_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticLiver_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic liver. It is much better than a biological liver in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLiver_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLiver_CAC.label>cultist bionic liver</OE_ProstheticLiver_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticLiver_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic liver. It is much better than a biological liver in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLiver_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLiver_OES.label>heroic bionic liver</OE_ProstheticLiver_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticLiver_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic liver. It is much better than a biological liver in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLiver_OES.description>

<!--=============== Lung ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLung.label>bionic lung</OE_ProstheticLung.label>
<OE_ProstheticLung.description>Obsidia bionic lung. It is better than a biological lung in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLung.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLung_M.label>advanced bionic lung</OE_ProstheticLung_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticLung_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic lung. It is much better than a biological lung in almost every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLung_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLung_CAC.label>cultist bionic lung</OE_ProstheticLung_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticLung_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic lung. It is much better than a biological lung in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLung_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticLung_OES.label>heroic bionic lung</OE_ProstheticLung_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticLung_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic lung. It is much better than a biological lung in every way. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticLung_OES.description>

<!--=============== Eyes ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticEye.label>bionic eye</OE_ProstheticEye.label>
<OE_ProstheticEye.description>Obsidia bionic eye. It is better than a biological eye in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticEye.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticEye_M.label>advanced bionic eye</OE_ProstheticEye_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticEye_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic eye. It is much better than a biological eye in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticEye_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticEye_CAC.label>cultist bionic eye</OE_ProstheticEye_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticEye_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic eye. It is much better than a biological eye in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticEye_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticEye_OES.label>heroic bionic eye</OE_ProstheticEye_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticEye_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic eye. It is much better than a biological eye in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticEye_OES.description>

<!--=============== Ears ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticEar.label>bionic ear</OE_ProstheticEar.label>
<OE_ProstheticEar.description>Obsidia bionic ear. It is better than a biological ear in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticEar.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticEar_M.label>advanced bionic ear</OE_ProstheticEar_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticEar_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic ear. It is much better than a biological ear in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticEar_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticEar_CAC.label>cultist bionic ear</OE_ProstheticEar_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticEar_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic ear. It is much better than a biological ear in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticEar_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticEar_OES.label>heroic bionic ear</OE_ProstheticEar_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticEar_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic ear. It is much better than a biological ear in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticEar_OES.description>

<!--=============== Jaw ====================-->
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Normal ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticJaw.label>bionic jaw</OE_ProstheticJaw.label>
<OE_ProstheticJaw.description>Obsidia bionic jaw. It is better than a biological jaw in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a small strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticJaw.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - Mod ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticJaw_M.label>advanced bionic jaw</OE_ProstheticJaw_M.label>
<OE_ProstheticJaw_M.description>Obsidia advanced bionic jaw. It is much better than a biological jaw in almost every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticJaw_M.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - CAC ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticJaw_CAC.label>cultist bionic jaw</OE_ProstheticJaw_CAC.label>
<OE_ProstheticJaw_CAC.description>Obsidia cultist bionic jaw. It is much better than a biological jaw in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticJaw_CAC.description>
<!--=============== Prosthetic - OES ====================-->
<OE_ProstheticJaw_OES.label>heroic bionic jaw</OE_ProstheticJaw_OES.label>
<OE_ProstheticJaw_OES.description>Obsidia heroic bionic jaw. It is much better than a biological jaw in every way. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. The use of this prosthesis puts a perceptible strain on the body.</OE_ProstheticJaw_OES.description>

</LanguageData>