<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<!--=============== Woods ====================-->
<OE_FungiPlankFloor.label>fungi floor</OE_FungiPlankFloor.label>
<OE_FungiPlankFloor.description>Excellent fungi wood flooring, beautiful enough, clean and universal due to its low chance of burning. Very easy to install.</OE_FungiPlankFloor.description>

<OE_DragonianPlankFloor.label>dragonian floor</OE_DragonianPlankFloor.label>
<OE_DragonianPlankFloor.description>Dragonian floor is highly prized by Obsidia nobility because of its luxury. Mostly used in hunting lodges.</OE_DragonianPlankFloor.description>

<!--=============== Metals ====================-->
<OE_ObsidianTile.label>obsidian tile</OE_ObsidianTile.label>
<OE_ObsidianTile.description>Standard obsidian floor is beautiful and clean. Very difficult to lay.</OE_ObsidianTile.description>

<OE_MythrilTile.label>mythril tile</OE_MythrilTile.label>
<OE_MythrilTile.description>Mythril tile is the most luxurious of the bunch and provides a small cleanliness bonus. Highly prized by Obsidia nobility.</OE_MythrilTile.description>

<OE_PlatinumTile.label>platinum tile</OE_PlatinumTile.label>
<OE_PlatinumTile.description>Sterile platinum floor with special cleanliness-enhancing properties. Extra-clean rooms improve outcomes in hospitals and research labs. This tile is very slow to build, but quick to clean.</OE_PlatinumTile.description>

<OE_EmpyriumTile.label>empyrium tile</OE_EmpyriumTile.label>
<OE_EmpyriumTile.description>Empyrium tile is the most luxurious of the bunch and provides a cleanliness bonus. Highly prized by Obsidia nobility.</OE_EmpyriumTile.description>

<OE_OrichalcumTile.label>orichalcum tile</OE_OrichalcumTile.label>
<OE_OrichalcumTile.description>Orichalcum tile is the most luxurious of the bunch and provides a cleanliness bonus. Highly prized by Obsidia nobility.</OE_OrichalcumTile.description>

<!--=============== Crystal Tilled Soil ====================-->
<OE_Crystal_TilledSoil.label>crystal tilled soil</OE_Crystal_TilledSoil.label>
<OE_Crystal_TilledSoil.description>Triple efficient tilled soil with Sinterius. Costly but effective Obsidia technique.</OE_Crystal_TilledSoil.description>
<OE_Crystal_TilledSoil.tools.dirt.label>dirt</OE_Crystal_TilledSoil.tools.dirt.label>

<!--=============== Metals Matrix ====================-->
<OE_ObsidianHexTile.label>obsidian matrix tile</OE_ObsidianHexTile.label>
<OE_ObsidianHexTile.description>Standard obsidian matrix tile is beautiful and clean. Very difficult to lay.</OE_ObsidianHexTile.description>

<OE_MythrilHexTile.label>mythril matrix tile</OE_MythrilHexTile.label>
<OE_MythrilHexTile.description>Mythril matrix tile is the most luxurious of the bunch and provides a small cleanliness bonus. Highly prized by Obsidia nobility.</OE_MythrilHexTile.description>

<OE_PlatinumHexTile.label>platinum matrix tile</OE_PlatinumHexTile.label>
<OE_PlatinumHexTile.description>Sterile platinum matrix tile with special cleanliness-enhancing properties. Extra-clean rooms improve outcomes in hospitals and research labs. This tile is very slow to build, but quick to clean.</OE_PlatinumHexTile.description>

<OE_EmpyriumHexTile.label>empyrium matrix tile</OE_EmpyriumHexTile.label>
<OE_EmpyriumHexTile.description>Empyrium matrix tile is the most luxurious of the bunch and provides a cleanliness bonus. Highly prized by Obsidia nobility.</OE_EmpyriumHexTile.description>

<OE_OrichalcumHexTile.label>orichalcum matrix tile</OE_OrichalcumHexTile.label>
<OE_OrichalcumHexTile.description>Orichalcum matrix tile is the most luxurious of the bunch and provides a cleanliness bonus. Highly prized by Obsidia nobility.</OE_OrichalcumHexTile.description>

</LanguageData>