<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
<!--=============== OE - Tree Pearlapple ====================-->
<Plant_OE_TreePearlapple.label>Pearlapple tree</Plant_OE_TreePearlapple.label>
<Plant_OE_TreePearlapple.description>Obsidias long-growing crystal tree bearing pearlapples. Pearlapple fruits used as a meat substitute.</Plant_OE_TreePearlapple.description>

<!--=============== OE - Tree Syntherius ====================-->
<Plant_OE_TreeSyntherius.label>Syntherius tree</Plant_OE_TreeSyntherius.label>
<Plant_OE_TreeSyntherius.description>Strange and previously underestimated plant from Obsidias. Syntherius crystals grow inside the tree. Previously, it was used in jewelry, but after further exploring the possibilities of this plant, it became a key element in the production of Obsidia.\n\nThe plant is medium size, which allows it to be grown under a roof.</Plant_OE_TreeSyntherius.description>

<!--=============== OE - Tree Fungi ====================-->
<Plant_OE_TreeFungi.label>Fungi tree</Plant_OE_TreeFungi.label>
<Plant_OE_TreeFungi.description>Huge Obsidias mushrooms that yield unique wood. This wood is more durable and less flammable.\n\nThey do not require a lot of space for growth, they can grow at a short distance from each other.</Plant_OE_TreeFungi.description>

<!--=============== OE - Tree Dragonian ====================-->
<Plant_OE_TreeDragonian.label>Dragonian tree</Plant_OE_TreeDragonian.label>
<Plant_OE_TreeDragonian.description>According to ancient legends, these trees grow in the burial places of ancient dragon-like creatures that inhabited Obsidia long before people appeared there. Very rare and valuable Obsidias tree of medium size. This tree yields a small amount of very valuable, durable and beautiful wood.\n\nIt can grow even on rocky terrain.</Plant_OE_TreeDragonian.description>

<!--=============== OE - Moonplant ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Moonplant.label>Moonplant</Plant_OE_Moonplant.label>
<Plant_OE_Moonplant.description>Obsidias mid-size crystal crop that yields silk net that is both difficult to tear and soft to the touch. These are used to make mooncloth.</Plant_OE_Moonplant.description>

<!--=============== OE - Jumy ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Jumy.label>Jumy</Plant_OE_Jumy.label>
<Plant_OE_Jumy.description>Small Obsidias plant inside which grows handfuls tasty and sweet berries.</Plant_OE_Jumy.description>

<!--=============== OE - Pellashroom ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Pellashroom.label>Pellashroom</Plant_OE_Pellashroom.label>
<Plant_OE_Pellashroom.description>Genetically modified Obsidias mushrooms. Produces a small amount of chemfuel.</Plant_OE_Pellashroom.description>

<!--=============== OE - Lotus ====================-->
<!--=============== Dusk ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Lotus_D.label>Dusk Lotus</Plant_OE_Lotus_D.label>
<Plant_OE_Lotus_D.description>Beautiful dark flowers of the Obsidias Lotus.</Plant_OE_Lotus_D.description>

<!--=============== Sunny ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Lotus_S.label>Sunny Lotus</Plant_OE_Lotus_S.label>
<Plant_OE_Lotus_S.description>Beautiful light flowers of the Obsidias Lotus.</Plant_OE_Lotus_S.description>

<!--=============== OE - Belladonna ====================-->
<!--=============== Tundral ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Tundral_B.label>Tundral Belladonna</Plant_OE_Tundral_B.label>
<Plant_OE_Tundral_B.description>Outlandish blue flower of Obsidias Belladonna. Can be used as a night light.</Plant_OE_Tundral_B.description>

<!--=============== Coral ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Coral_B.label>Coral Belladonna</Plant_OE_Coral_B.label>
<Plant_OE_Coral_B.description>Outlandish pink flower of Obsidias Belladonna. Can be used as a night light.</Plant_OE_Coral_B.description>

<!--=============== Alpine ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Alpine_B.label>Alpine Belladonna</Plant_OE_Alpine_B.label>
<Plant_OE_Alpine_B.description>Outlandish yellow flower of Obsidias Belladonna. Can be used as a night light.</Plant_OE_Alpine_B.description>

<!--=============== Oasis ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Oasis_B.label>Oasis Belladonna</Plant_OE_Oasis_B.label>
<Plant_OE_Oasis_B.description>Outlandish green flower of Obsidias Belladonna. Can be used as a night light.</Plant_OE_Oasis_B.description>

<!--=============== Bloody ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Bloody_B.label>Bloody Belladonna</Plant_OE_Bloody_B.label>
<Plant_OE_Bloody_B.description>Gloomy red flower of Obsidias Belladonna. Can be used as a night light.</Plant_OE_Bloody_B.description>

<!--=============== OE - Iglolia ====================-->
<Plant_OE_Iglolia.label>iglolia</Plant_OE_Iglolia.label>
<Plant_OE_Iglolia.description>A fast-growing vines that grows in Obsidias dense groves. Iglolia can be harvested for a wood-like material. The plant itself is not beautiful.</Plant_OE_Iglolia.description>

<!--=============== OE - JumyBush ====================-->
<Plant_OE_JumyBush.label>jumy bush</Plant_OE_JumyBush.label>
<Plant_OE_JumyBush.description>An artificially bred medium Obsidias plant inside which grows handfuls tasty and sweet berries.</Plant_OE_JumyBush.description>

<!--=============== OE - MyceliumStump ====================-->
<Plant_OE_MyceliumStump.label>mycelium stump</Plant_OE_MyceliumStump.label>
<Plant_OE_MyceliumStump.description>An artificially bred symbiosis of tree and mycelium form Obsidia. Doesn't grow very fast, but can be an excellent source of raw fungus.</Plant_OE_MyceliumStump.description>

<!--=============== OE - Tree Pearlpeach ====================-->
<Plant_OE_TreePearlpeach.label>Pearlpeach tree</Plant_OE_TreePearlpeach.label>
<Plant_OE_TreePearlpeach.description>Obsidias long-growing toxin-adapted crystal tree bearing pearlpeach. Pearlpeach fruits used as a meat substitute. It can only grow in polluted areas.</Plant_OE_TreePearlpeach.description>

<!--=============== OE - Toxi Jumy ====================-->
<Plant_OE_ToxiJumy.label>toxi Jumy</Plant_OE_ToxiJumy.label>
<Plant_OE_ToxiJumy.description>Small toxin-adapted Obsidias plant inside which grows handfuls tasty and sweet berries. It can only grow in polluted areas.</Plant_OE_ToxiJumy.description>

<!--=============== OE - Toxi JumyBush ====================-->
<Plant_OE_ToxiJumyBush.label>toxi Jumy bush</Plant_OE_ToxiJumyBush.label>
<Plant_OE_ToxiJumyBush.description>An artificially bred medium toxin-adapted Obsidias plant inside which grows handfuls tasty and sweet berries. It can only grow in polluted areas.</Plant_OE_ToxiJumyBush.description>

<!--=============== Succulent of Doom ====================-->
<!--=============== Flower ====================-->
<Plant_OE_SucculentOfDoom_Flower.label>Succulent of Doom's flower</Plant_OE_SucculentOfDoom_Flower.label>
<Plant_OE_SucculentOfDoom_Flower.description>No one expected doom to come in a flowerpot. The digital artist, known online as @LNS_OWL for her adorable illustrations, once bought a charming little succulent set from a group of wandering traders. At first, it was just a bit of greenery to brighten her windowsill. But soon, tiny sprouts began appearing—everywhere. She kept repotting them, one by one, into new pots. Season after season, the pots multiplied, slowly overtaking shelves, desks, and every sunlit surface. Now her cozy studio is a labyrinth of leafy tenants… and the plants are still looking for more space.\n\nFortunately, it only grows in polluted areas.</Plant_OE_SucculentOfDoom_Flower.description>
<!--=============== Grass ====================-->
<Plant_OE_SucculentOfDoom_Grass.label>Succulent of Doom's grass</Plant_OE_SucculentOfDoom_Grass.label>
<Plant_OE_SucculentOfDoom_Grass.description>This creeping grass is spread by the flower’s roots—quietly, steadily—like it's helping its potted brethren colonize everything soft and green. By the time you notice it, your home is no longer yours—it’s theirs.</Plant_OE_SucculentOfDoom_Grass.description>

</LanguageData>