<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<LanguageData>
<!--=============== Biophormids ====================-->
<!--=============== Labryscid ====================-->
<OE_Labryscid.label>labryscid</OE_Labryscid.label>
<OE_Labryscid.description>A small, non-combat worker-class insectoid, the Labryscid fulfills essential hive duties without engaging in battle. Biophormids are the results of genetic experimentation by the android David in the Obsidia Empire. Initially considered failures, these insectoids were in fact David’s deliberate creation, intended as his legacy in the form of a new life form.\n\nDespite its lack of combat skills, the Labryscid is the backbone of the hive, tirelessly working to maintain the infrastructure and ensure the survival of its more dangerous counterparts.</OE_Labryscid.description>
<OE_Labryscid.tools.left_hand.label>left hand</OE_Labryscid.tools.left_hand.label>
<OE_Labryscid.tools.right_hand.label>right hand</OE_Labryscid.tools.right_hand.label>
<OE_Labryscid.tools.mandibles.label>mandibles</OE_Labryscid.tools.mandibles.label>
<OE_Labryscid.tools.head.label>head</OE_Labryscid.tools.head.label>

<!--=============== Razorsythe ====================-->
<OE_Razorsythe.label>razorsythe</OE_Razorsythe.label>
<OE_Razorsythe.description>This medium-sized warrior-class insectoid serves as the frontline soldier for hive defense and attack, wielding an amalgam knife. Biophormids are the results of genetic experimentation by the android David in the Obsidia Empire. Initially considered failures, these insectoids were in fact David’s deliberate creation, intended as his legacy in the form of a new life form.\n\nRazorsythe operates as the hive’s primary defensive force, using swift strikes with its knife to fend off threats or lead attacks on enemies. Its dedication to the hive is unmatched, sacrificing itself without hesitation.</OE_Razorsythe.description>
<OE_Razorsythe.tools.left_hand.label>left hand</OE_Razorsythe.tools.left_hand.label>
<OE_Razorsythe.tools.right_hand.label>right hand</OE_Razorsythe.tools.right_hand.label>
<OE_Razorsythe.tools.mandibles.label>mandibles</OE_Razorsythe.tools.mandibles.label>
<OE_Razorsythe.tools.head.label>head</OE_Razorsythe.tools.head.label>

<!--=============== Winglance ====================-->
<OE_Winglance.label>winglance</OE_Winglance.label>
<OE_Winglance.description>A medium-sized hunter-class insectoid, Winglance is known for its agility and ability to fly, using its wings to move quickly while armed with an amalgam SMG. Biophormids are the results of genetic experimentation by the android David in the Obsidia Empire. Initially considered failures, these insectoids were in fact David’s deliberate creation, intended as his legacy in the form of a new life form.\n\nWinglance excels in swift, precise strikes from the air. Its mobility makes it a perfect scout and assassin, often ambushing prey with deadly accuracy before retreating into the sky.</OE_Winglance.description>
<OE_Winglance.tools.left_hand.label>left hand</OE_Winglance.tools.left_hand.label>
<OE_Winglance.tools.right_hand.label>right hand</OE_Winglance.tools.right_hand.label>
<OE_Winglance.tools.mandibles.label>mandibles</OE_Winglance.tools.mandibles.label>
<OE_Winglance.tools.head.label>head</OE_Winglance.tools.head.label>

<!--=============== Brontarok ====================-->
<OE_Brontarok.label>brontarok</OE_Brontarok.label>
<OE_Brontarok.description>A large, heavily-armored defender-class insectoid, Brontarok moves slowly but is nearly impervious to damage, wielding a massive amalgam scythe. Biophormids are the results of genetic experimentation by the android David in the Obsidia Empire. Initially considered failures, these insectoids were in fact David’s deliberate creation, intended as his legacy in the form of a new life form.\n\nBrontarok’s thick chitinous armor makes it a fortress on legs, designed to absorb blows while methodically cutting through enemies with its immense scythe. Slow but relentless, it protects the hive from any that dare approach.</OE_Brontarok.description>
<OE_Brontarok.tools.left_hand.label>left hand</OE_Brontarok.tools.left_hand.label>
<OE_Brontarok.tools.right_hand.label>right hand</OE_Brontarok.tools.right_hand.label>
<OE_Brontarok.tools.mandibles.label>mandibles</OE_Brontarok.tools.mandibles.label>
<OE_Brontarok.tools.head.label>head</OE_Brontarok.tools.head.label>

<!--=============== Swarmella ====================-->
<OE_Swarmella.label>swarmella</OE_Swarmella.label>
<OE_Swarmella.description>A medium-sized, female-only hunter-class insectoid, Swarmella acts as a queen within the hive, summoning Pincerlin drones to fight alongside her and wielding an amalgam scepter. Biophormids are the results of genetic experimentation by the android David in the Obsidia Empire. Initially considered failures, these insectoids were in fact David’s deliberate creation, intended as his legacy in the form of a new life form.\n\nSwarmella’s ability to summon small drones in battle and her strategic control of the battlefield make her both a powerful ally and a feared opponent. Her regal presence commands respect, ensuring that her Pincerlin swarm never strays far from her defense.</OE_Swarmella.description>
<OE_Swarmella.tools.left_hand.label>left hand</OE_Swarmella.tools.left_hand.label>
<OE_Swarmella.tools.right_hand.label>right hand</OE_Swarmella.tools.right_hand.label>
<OE_Swarmella.tools.mandibles.label>mandibles</OE_Swarmella.tools.mandibles.label>
<OE_Swarmella.tools.head.label>head</OE_Swarmella.tools.head.label>

<!--=============== Pincerlin ====================-->
<OE_Pincerlin.label>pincerlin</OE_Pincerlin.label>
<OE_Pincerlin.description>A small, drone-class insectoid, Pincerlin is summoned by Swarmella to assist her in battle, often used for her personal protection. Biophormids are the results of genetic experimentation by the android David in the Obsidia Empire. Initially considered failures, these insectoids were in fact David’s deliberate creation, intended as his legacy in the form of a new life form.\n\nThough tiny, Pincerlin plays a crucial role in Swarmella’s survival, swarming her enemies with bites and stings. Individually weak, they are deadly in numbers, overwhelming foes with sheer tenacity.</OE_Pincerlin.description>
<OE_Pincerlin.tools.mandibles.label>mandibles</OE_Pincerlin.tools.mandibles.label>
<OE_Pincerlin.tools.head.label>head</OE_Pincerlin.tools.head.label>

<!--=============== Monarchid ====================-->
<OE_Monarchid.label>monarchid</OE_Monarchid.label>
<OE_Monarchid.description>A medium-sized, male-only boss-class insectoid, Monarchid is the true ruler of the hive, wielding an amalgam sniper rifle and commanding with absolute authority. Biophormids are the results of genetic experimentation by the android David in the Obsidia Empire. Initially considered failures, these insectoids were in fact David’s deliberate creation, intended as his legacy in the form of a new life form.\n\nMonarchid’s rule is absolute, and his sharp, strategic mind is matched only by his deadliness in combat. Unlike other Biophormids, Monarchid possesses a unique intelligence, often seen overseeing the hive’s activities from a distance, calculating every move with cold precision. His amalgam sniper rifle allows him to eliminate threats long before they can approach the hive, but he is equally dangerous in close combat. The weapon is an extension of his will, capable of shifting between long-range precision shots and devastating melee strikes when enemies get too close.\n\nLegends among the Biophormids speak of Monarchid as the firstborn of David’s "children," crafted with a blend of superior genes to become the perfect ruler. His loyalty to the hive is unwavering, but he also harbors a deep sense of responsibility toward the legacy of David, seeing himself as the continuation of his creator’s vision. When Monarchid fights, it is not only to defend his hive but also to uphold the purpose for which he was designed: the perfection of their species. His decisions are final, and any opposition within the hive is met with swift, brutal consequences. Monarchid’s reign is one of calculated dominance, ensuring that the hive thrives under his unchallenged authority.</OE_Monarchid.description>
<OE_Monarchid.tools.left_hand.label>left hand</OE_Monarchid.tools.left_hand.label>
<OE_Monarchid.tools.right_hand.label>right hand</OE_Monarchid.tools.right_hand.label>
<OE_Monarchid.tools.mandibles.label>mandibles</OE_Monarchid.tools.mandibles.label>
<OE_Monarchid.tools.head.label>head</OE_Monarchid.tools.head.label>

</LanguageData>