<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
<!--=============== OE - Trophy Grimoire ====================-->
<!--=============== Various ====================-->
<!--=============== Worker ====================-->
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Worker.label>Grimoire of Reconstruction</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Worker.label>
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Worker.description>Grimoires are enigmatic artifacts, forged from unknown relics during the final days of Obsidia's Last War. Each was crafted with a singular purpose by a unique mind—some brilliant, some mad, all unforgettable. It's said that those who carry a Grimoire often find themselves speaking to it, unconsciously, as if the book listens. Whispers claim that the soul of each creator remains bound within their work, waiting... watching.\n\nCrafted by Sophie Neuenmuller, the chief architect responsible for rebuilding Obsidia’s shattered capital. When given access to relic technology, she saw not a weapon, but an opportunity to hasten healing and progress. Her Grimoire became a blueprint of her unwavering dedication to restoration, encoded with the will to rebuild what was lost.\n\nGrants an energy shield for protection. Emits an aura working stats for allies and the owner within 24 tiles.</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Worker.description>

<!--=============== Ranged ====================-->
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Ranged.label>Grimoire of the Marksman</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Ranged.label>
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Ranged.description>Grimoires are enigmatic artifacts, forged from unknown relics during the final days of Obsidia's Last War. Each was crafted with a singular purpose by a unique mind—some brilliant, some mad, all unforgettable. It's said that those who carry a Grimoire often find themselves speaking to it, unconsciously, as if the book listens. Whispers claim that the soul of each creator remains bound within their work, waiting... watching.\n\nForged by Varric Tethras, a legendary marksman and the soul of his recon squad. He poured his battlefield instincts and leadership into the tome, embedding strategies, formations, and wisdom learned in blood. To hold it is to hear the calm voice of a commander watching over your shoulder.\n\nGrants an energy shield for protection. Emits an aura boosting ranged combat stats for allies and the owner within 24 tiles.</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Ranged.description>

<!--=============== Melee ====================-->
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Melee.label>Grimoire of the Steel Soul</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Melee.label>
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Melee.description>Grimoires are enigmatic artifacts, forged from unknown relics during the final days of Obsidia's Last War. Each was crafted with a singular purpose by a unique mind—some brilliant, some mad, all unforgettable. It's said that those who carry a Grimoire often find themselves speaking to it, unconsciously, as if the book listens. Whispers claim that the soul of each creator remains bound within their work, waiting... watching.\n\nAsta, once a nameless labor slave, rose through sheer tenacity to become a melee legend. He forged his Grimoire not in a lab, but on the battlefield, tempering it with every wound and victory. It is not a record of power, but a testament to a will that refused to break.\n\nGrants an energy shield for protection. Emits an aura boosting melee combat stats for allies and the owner within 24 tiles.</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Melee.description>

<!--=============== Defender ====================-->
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Defender.label>Grimoire of Sanctum</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Defender.label>
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Defender.description>Grimoires are enigmatic artifacts, forged from unknown relics during the final days of Obsidia's Last War. Each was crafted with a singular purpose by a unique mind—some brilliant, some mad, all unforgettable. It's said that those who carry a Grimoire often find themselves speaking to it, unconsciously, as if the book listens. Whispers claim that the soul of each creator remains bound within their work, waiting... watching.\n\nThe Winchester brothers, twin hunters of the dark, discovered the means to create a Grimoire during a grim expedition. What they found disturbed them—rituals too close to soulbinding, too intimate with death. Yet together, they made their Grimoire, sealing within it a legacy of protection, sacrifice, and brotherhood.\n\nGrants an energy shield for protection. Emits an aura boosting defensive stats for allies and the owner within 24 tiles.</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Defender.description>

<!--=============== Psy ====================-->
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Psy.label>Grimoire of Mental Supremacy</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Psy.label>
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Psy.description>Grimoires are enigmatic artifacts, forged from unknown relics during the final days of Obsidia's Last War. Each was crafted with a singular purpose by a unique mind—some brilliant, some mad, all unforgettable. It's said that those who carry a Grimoire often find themselves speaking to it, unconsciously, as if the book listens. Whispers claim that the soul of each creator remains bound within their work, waiting... watching.\n\nBorn of nobility, Balthazar Blake defied tradition by fighting on the frontlines with his psionic gifts. Respected by soldiers, feared by aristocrats, he became a beacon of mental might and moral clarity. In his final years, he wove his memories and essence into his Grimoire, a final act of service to the minds yet to awaken.\n\nGrants an energy shield for protection. Emits an aura boosting psy stats for allies and the owner within 24 tiles.</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Psy.description>

<!--=============== Social ====================-->
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Social.label>Grimoire of Royal Echo</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Social.label>
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Social.description>Grimoires are enigmatic artifacts, forged from unknown relics during the final days of Obsidia's Last War. Each was crafted with a singular purpose by a unique mind—some brilliant, some mad, all unforgettable. It's said that those who carry a Grimoire often find themselves speaking to it, unconsciously, as if the book listens. Whispers claim that the soul of each creator remains bound within their work, waiting... watching.\n\nSei Takanashi, a princess known more for elegance than seriousness, was dared to try her hand at Grimoire-making. Against all odds—and to the embarrassment of her critics—she succeeded. Her creation became a masterwork of charm and influence, infused with the quiet force that moves empires without bloodshed.\n\nGrants an energy shield for protection. Emits an aura boosting social stats for allies and the owner within 24 tiles.</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Social.description>

<!--=============== Mechanitor ====================-->
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Mechanitor.label>Grimoire of Integration</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Mechanitor.label>
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Mechanitor.description>Grimoires are enigmatic artifacts, forged from unknown relics during the final days of Obsidia's Last War. Each was crafted with a singular purpose by a unique mind—some brilliant, some mad, all unforgettable. It's said that those who carry a Grimoire often find themselves speaking to it, unconsciously, as if the book listens. Whispers claim that the soul of each creator remains bound within their work, waiting... watching.\n\nClementine was a recluse who abandoned humanity for machinery, driven by obsession and perhaps something deeper. Her Grimoire was assembled in silence, among machines she called kin, without witnesses or fanfare. It hums with alien logic and devotion to synthetic perfection, rejecting the weakness of flesh.\n\nDoes not emit an aura, but boosting mechanitor stats and enhances control over mechanoids.</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Mechanitor.description>

<!--=============== Scientist ====================-->
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Scientist.label>Grimoire of Forbidden Insight</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Scientist.label>
<OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Scientist.description>Grimoires are enigmatic artifacts, forged from unknown relics during the final days of Obsidia's Last War. Each was crafted with a singular purpose by a unique mind—some brilliant, some mad, all unforgettable. It's said that those who carry a Grimoire often find themselves speaking to it, unconsciously, as if the book listens. Whispers claim that the soul of each creator remains bound within their work, waiting... watching.\n\nNo one knows who created this Grimoire, or why their memory has vanished so completely. Found on a flawless Mythril desk, beside a single blood-written word—Yog-Sothoth—the book seems to radiate secrecy itself. Scholars who study it claim it watches them back, offering brilliance at a cost they cannot name.\n\nGrants an energy shield for protection. Emits an aura boosting research stats for allies and the owner within 24 tiles.</OE_Trophy_Grimoire_Scientist.description>

</LanguageData>