<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
<!--=============== Artificial Ecosystem Small ====================-->
<OE_ArtEcosysMicro_Sun.label>small obsidia artificial ecosystem (sun)</OE_ArtEcosysMicro_Sun.label>
<OE_ArtEcosysMicro_Sun.description>Provides plants grow faster planted in this small artificial ecosystem due Obsidia technologies. Requires a high amount of power to work; plants will die if power is cut. Contains a built-in sun lamp to provide light for the plants.</OE_ArtEcosysMicro_Sun.description>

<OE_ArtEcosysMicro_Dusk.label>small obsidia artificial ecosystem (dusk)</OE_ArtEcosysMicro_Dusk.label>
<OE_ArtEcosysMicro_Dusk.description>Provides plants grow faster planted in this small artificial ecosystem due Obsidia technologies. Requires a high amount of power to work; plants will die if power is cut.</OE_ArtEcosysMicro_Dusk.description>

<!--=============== Artificial Ecosystem Medium ====================-->
<OE_ArtEcosysMedium_Sun.label>obsidia artificial ecosystem (sun)</OE_ArtEcosysMedium_Sun.label>
<OE_ArtEcosysMedium_Sun.description>Provides plants grow faster planted in this artificial ecosystem due Obsidia technologies. Requires a high amount of power to work; plants will die if power is cut. Contains a built-in sun lamp to provide light for the plants.</OE_ArtEcosysMedium_Sun.description>

<OE_ArtEcosysMedium_Dusk.label>obsidia artificial ecosystem (dusk)</OE_ArtEcosysMedium_Dusk.label>
<OE_ArtEcosysMedium_Dusk.description>Provides plants grow faster planted in this artificial ecosystem due Obsidia technologies. Requires a high amount of power to work; plants will die if power is cut.</OE_ArtEcosysMedium_Dusk.description>

<!--=============== Artificial Ecosystem Large ====================-->
<OE_ArtEcosysLarge_Sun.label>large obsidia artificial ecosystem (sun)</OE_ArtEcosysLarge_Sun.label>
<OE_ArtEcosysLarge_Sun.description>Provides plants grow faster planted in this large artificial ecosystem due Obsidia technologies. Requires a high amount of power to work; plants will die if power is cut. Contains a built-in sun lamp to provide light for the plants.</OE_ArtEcosysLarge_Sun.description>

<OE_ArtEcosysLarge_Dusk.label>large obsidia artificial ecosystem (dusk)</OE_ArtEcosysLarge_Dusk.label>
<OE_ArtEcosysLarge_Dusk.description>Provides plants grow faster planted in this large artificial ecosystem due Obsidia technologies. Requires a high amount of power to work; plants will die if power is cut.</OE_ArtEcosysLarge_Dusk.description>

</LanguageData>